

WILSON NGO

CONTACT

REFERENCES

0434-863-805

0416 919 119 WILSONNGO0911@GMAIL.COM MELBOURNE, VIC

SANDY TRUONG
MCDONALD'S ASSISTANT RESTAURANT MANAGER (SUNSHINE)
0421-222-295
REX RAKEI
MCDONALD'S MANAGER (SUNSHINE)
0451-094-159
PHUNG VU
CO DO OWNER (RICHMOND)

PROFILE

Experienced Crew Trainer successful at operating in a high-volume, fast paced environment. Adaptable, practiced at adjusting to changing specifications by evaluating orders and updating procedures to meet new targets. Results-driven and forward-thinking in checking forecasts and orders for new directives. Bringing experience as a versatile and hardworking team member.

EXPERIENCE

CO DO

CASUAL WAITER: 04/2017 - 05/2017

- Seating and greeting customers at tables
- · Cleaning tables, floors, cups, dishes
- · Setting tablesStocking up cutlery, sauces
- Engaging in customer service

MCDONALDS SUNSHINE

CREW TRAINER: 03/2018 - 06/2020

- Processed POS transactions, including checks, cash and credit purchases or refunds.
- Accurately record all cash movements while following policies on large note transactions and cash out
- Regularly assessed sales floor stock levels to replenish with backstock merchandise before depletion
- Consistently provided friendly service to promote better customer engagement
- Trained new hires to perform cross-training exercises with experienced workers and mentored junior employees to improve performance, food safety and customer service
- Cleaning: Attended to daily shift cleaning duties including general cleaning, rubbish removal and floor mopping to meet both HACCP and Food Safety RegulationStock up kitchen with products including boxes 15kgs+

EDUCATION

ST. BERNADETTE'S PRIMARY SCHOOL, SUNSHINE NORTH, VIC - 2007-2013
BRAYBROOK SECONDARY COLLEGE, BRAYBROOK, VIC - 2014-2019
RMIT UNIVERSITY, 2020-2021
CODER ACEDEMY, PRESENT

SKILLS

- · Order management
- Staff training
- Leadership
- Initiative
- High level of organisation
- Verbal and written communication
- Able to lift heavy boxes (15kgs+)

AWARDS + CERTIFICATES

[2017] NAMED THE "EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH" AWARD @MCDONALD'S

[2017] Safe@work Certificate
[2017] Australian Red Cross Community Service Certificate
[2019] VCE Certificate
[2019] Year 12 Certificate
[2020] Agiles Way of Working Certificate
[2020] Emotional intelligence Certificate